Gan'er, Gan'er.
Mom.
You're so badly hurt.
How could they be so vicious?
Ning Chen, he...
He held an unauthorized trial,
and brutally tortured me.
He abused his power!
You must get justice for me, Mom.
Father, look at Gan'er.
Grandfather.
You must get justice for us.
Yes, Grandfather.
Grandfather.
Take him to be treated.
Go, quickly.
Mom, go on, go on.
Hurry, hurry.
Silver Guard Ning.
Quite the impressive display.
Even to your own kin,
you can be this ruthless.
You overstate it, Left Chancellor.
Half-brothers
hardly count as kin.
Besides,
Paid by the Emperor,
blessed by His grace,
I must set an example,
and not bend the law for personal gain.
You, on the other hand—
cut off the tail to survive.
What a clever scheme.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Left Chancellor,
Men act,
and Heaven is watching.
We'll see about that.
Father,
how could he utter
such treasonous words?
Whatever you have to say,
save it for home.
Yes.
Commander Geng,
I shall take my leave.
I won't see you out.
From now on,
the feud between Ning Chen and the Left Chancellor
will come out into the open.
You didn't say anything, did you?
Rest assured, Father.
I didn't breathe a single word.
Remember,
as long as I'm here,
I'll keep you all safe.
But Father,
that bastard is getting more brazen.
His Majesty sent him to quell bandits in Lingzhou.
What if he finds out about his mother—
I have my own plans.
Get over here.
Father-in-law.
You can't even protect your own wife and son.
What a useless wretch.
Father-in-law, please calm your anger.
Ning Ziming,
you'd better remember this.
If you ever let my daughter
and grandson suffer again,
don't blame me for being merciless.
Rest assured, Father-in-law.
This will never happen again.
Madam,
Ning Chen will set out for war soon.
You have men at the front.
By whatever means necessary,
he must not return to the capital alive.
Rest assured.
Commander Geng.
You wanted to see me?
For this campaign,
Lao Pan,
Ziping,
and Qi Zheng
will go with you
to keep you safe.
Them?
Maybe we should forget it.
They're great at investigations,
but they're amateurs on the battlefield.
Weapons have no eyes on the battlefield.
You need a few men you can trust.
This is also His Majesty's wish.
Fine, then.
You're all off duty for the next few days.
Go home and prepare.
Yes, sir.
And one more thing.
The men of the Imperial Inspectorate
must come back alive.
Understood.
Get the hell out.
My lord.
You're here.
Come find me next time.
Master Ning.
Ning Chen, let's have a chat.
Please.
No wonder they say the Music Bureau
is the biggest money-sink in the capital.
It's even more lavish than my Eastern Palace.
Comparing a brothel to the Eastern Palace?
You're really something.
Dear Ning, you're here.
Die'er.
This must be Miss Yudie.
I greet you, Master.
No need for formalities.
Rumor has it
the Music Bureau has Twelve Chambers,
and the ladies of each chamber
are all peerless beauties.
Meeting Miss Yudie today,
I see the rumors are true.
I hear Miss Yudie's pipa playing
is unmatched in the capital.
Might I have the honor?
No, you may not.
Be glad you're getting wine.
And you want my woman to play for you?
You...
Should I dance to liven things up too?
No, thank you.
Die'er.
Could you please
prepare some fine wine and food for us?
Of course, Dear Ning.
Have a seat.
Ning Chen,
you're a lucky man with the ladies.
The Twelve Chambers of the Music Bureau
have more than just Yudie and Nanzhi.
The other ladies
are all stunning beauties too.
Why don't I find one for you?
Forget it.
Coming to the Music Bureau is already going too far.
What do you mean?
One hundred taels per cup.
No.
What kind of wine is this?
Wine of friendship.
Friendship is priceless.
Well said.
Stop counting.
A friend arrives from afar,
is that not a joy?
Today,
I'll make sure you drink to your heart's content.
Come on.
Ning Chen.
The only one bold enough to snatch silver from me,
in all of Great Xuan,
is you.
I have to think
of how to punish you.
How about this?
I'll punish myself with three cups.
Sound fair?
In your dreams.
Six hundred taels in total.
Six cups of wine.
Three each.
No cheating.
So stingy.
So stingy, and you call yourself the Crown Prince?
Greetings, Crown Prince.
This humble one didn't know it was Your Highness.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
No need for formalities.
Rise.
Don't be nervous.
He's a good guy.
But he's the Crown Prince!
The future Xuandi.
Dear Ning is so close with him?
That's amazing.
Dear Ning.
I hear the Northern Frontier is colder than the capital.
I
had some thick robes made for you.
There's a scented sachet inside.
I made it myself.
I hope you like it, Dear Ning.
Of course I do.
Don't worry about me.
I'm blessed with great fortune.
Wait for my triumphant return.
You take good care of yourself.
I'll be waiting for you.
All right.
The battlefield is treacherous.
Huai'an asked me to tell you,
to be extra careful.
Who's Huai'an?
A ringleader. Not important.
I've just had drinks with him a few times.
Come on.
Crown Prince.
Let's drink. Come on.
These six cups,
today we won't stop till we're drunk.
No.
You can't drink from that.
You've got to use this.
No.
Since you've bought my Yudie's wine today,
we two won't stop till we're drunk.
Come on.
Cheers.
Drink up!
You little rascal.
With that armor on,
you really look like I did back in my day.
Bold and resolute.
When you return,
I'll have a surprise for you.
All right.
Verbal Edict from His Majesty.
Wait, wait, wait.
His Majesty said,
no need to kneel.
He told you to stand and listen.
His Majesty said,
take good care of yourself on the road,
and come back safe and sound.
Get your ass back here alive to see Me.
This general will do as you command.
And one more thing.
Thrifty at home, generous on the road.
Take this money with you.
This is...
This is what I've saved up for ages.
Don't go wasting it.
You...
You must come back alive.
Come back alive to see me.
Thank you, Uncle Quan.
Let's go.
Old General.
While I'm away from the capital,
I'd like to trouble you, Old General,
to look after Yudie and Xiao Mei for me.
If anyone dares to cross them,
please make a note of it, Old General.
When I return,
I'll settle the score with each of them.
Don't you worry.
You'd better take care of yourself first.
I'm off.
Dear Ning.
My Pan.
The east wind blows,
the war drums sound,
the beauty grows tipsy,
longing for your return.
News of victory soars,
the hero comes home.
May I be the bright moon walking by your side,
May moonbeams light your way each night.